a10networks.com 2014-06-15

# Privacy Policy

**Last Updated Date: January 1, 2014**

A10 Networks, Inc. ("A10 Networks," "we," "us") provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of this website located at www.A10 Networks.com ("Site"). Please note that this Privacy Policy only applies to this Site. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. 

By using our Site you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing" means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information and transferring it to the United States and internationally. 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please [contact us](http://info.a10networks.com/General_Inquiries.html). 

## Information Collection and Use

Our primary goal in collecting personally identifiable information is to provide you with information that you request from us via your use of the Site, including, without limitation, the provision of information about A10 Networks when you register products with A10, register for a A10 Networks account, when you use certain A10 products or services, when you request information about A10 Networks products or services, when you request certain documents, when you request to attend a training session or class or other hosted events, when request ask to be included in an email or other mailing list, and responding to queries about, or applications for, job listings. 

## Personally Identifiable Information

In general, it is not necessary to provide us with your personally identifiable information to use the Site. There are certain services we offer, however, which require the submission of personally identifiable information, such as your name, physical address, and email address. If you contact us by email through the Site, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you. We also use your personally identifiable information to send you other publications or information about our products that may be of interest to you. In addition, we may send you important administrative information regarding the Site and/or services we offer via the Site. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please [contact us](http://info.a10networks.com/General_Inquiries.html) to unsubscribe or opt-out. 

## Log Data

When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting as Internet domain and host names; operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider (or "ISP"), the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use it to monitor use of the Site and the services we offer via the Site and for the Site’s technical administration. 

## Cookies

Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and the services we offer via the Site. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. However, IP addresses are collected by the use of cookies. We mainly use "session cookies", which enable certain features of the Site and services we offer via the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and services we offer via the Site, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and services we offer via the Site. This session cookie is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Service Providers. A10 Networks may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the provision of services via the Site, or to perform certain Site-related services (e.g. hosting and maintenance services, database management and improvement of the Site’s features). We may from time to time share your personally identifiable information with such third parties to administer or complete these tasks. These third parties only have access to your information as necessary to perform their functions and may not use it for any other purpose. 

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. A10 Networks may need to access or disclose your personal information to comply with the law or legal process and to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

A10 Networks may share personal information and any additional information available to us in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Intel's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

Business Transfers. If any or all of the assets of A10 Networks are acquired by, or merged with another entity, we will share some or all of your information with this entity. 

## Security

A10 Networks is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. We will disclose any compromise of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored "personal data" (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system. 

## International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. 

## Links to Other Sites

Our Site may contain links to other websites including those of our clients. If you choose to visit an advertiser by "clicking on" a link or other type of advertisement, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. This Privacy Policy addresses the use and disclosure of information that we collect from you through this Site. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

## Our Policy Towards Children

This Site is not directed to children under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should [contact us](http://info.a10networks.com/General_Inquiries.html). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will remove such information from our files. 

## Contacting A10 Networks

If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact A10 Networks at:   
A10 Networks, Inc.   
3 West Plumeria Drive   
San Jose, California 95134   
Tel: 408 325-8668
